[theme music playing]
Frankly, I don't care
if your mother's dead.
And besides, you know? She deserves it.
Your mom was a slut.
[Julio] Didn't it cross your mind
you could've gotten yourself
killed doing this?
[Diego] I'm not afraid to die.
-[Julio] Then I won't kill you just yet.
-Papa!
[Julio] I'll make you feel just
how much you deserve to suffer.
[Carlotta] She will find a way to give
her family the justice they deserve.
If you're going to fight the Ardientes,
then I won't let you go alone.
I'll fight with you.
[Loring] How could you let this
happen to your son?!
[Diego] I want to find my relatives.
My biological relatives.
[Loring] That's Rosario. Your mother.
[Ivy] We need them, Mom.
All three of them will testify
against the Ardientes
Ivy, we have the same goal now.
Let's take them to court.
The right punishment for the Ardientes
isn't written in the law.
[Fernan] Diego and I saw the congressman.
He's running the gambling den
in this town.
We'll form a group. We'll take back
from the Ardientes what's rightfully ours.
[reporter] Attorney, what
can you say to the Ardientes?
[Georgina] We're coming for all of you.
[Emilia] Who's behind this?
Camia Cruz.
[Nimfa] Diego, it's Dad.
I heard they're going to attack
the congressman's gambling den!
No one else should know about this.
If the Ardientes find out
that Mister Fernan
is going against them,
your father's life will be at risk.
But, don't worry. I'll go after them.
[grunting]
[tense music playing]
[indistinct shouting]
[Fernan] Let's go!
[Fernan] Stay right here!
Look for the others.
Where's Mister Dolfo? Look for him!
[Fernan groans]
[Diego] Come on. We're almost out of here.
[Fernan] Where are the others? Help them.
-[Diego] Hurry up, Fernan.
-[Fernan groans]
[Diego] Move it.
-[Fernan] Is everybody here?
-[farmer 1] I think so.
You can't take this Thursday off.
[bodyguard] All right, sir.
[Jepoy] Governor.
Madrigal.
Why are there so many cars outside?
What's the occasion?
Congressman invited the members
of the party list here.
Oh. What about me? Didn't he invite me?
I'm afraid not, Governor.
Can I talk to him?
-[Julio] Arnaldo.
-Grandpa.
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
-Governor.
-[William] Congressman.
It's so nice of you to come.
My pleasure, as always.
Thank you. Anyway, the--
May I please speak with my father?
[William] As you please.
-Thank you.
-[Julio] Just a moment.
Emilia, what do you want from me?
So, you're having a party, Papa.
Yes, I am, and obviously,
you're not invited.
Yes, I noticed.
Anyway, Papa,
did you watch the news earlier?
Of course, I'm always watching the news.
And?
Oh, you want my opinion?
Well, if you would ask me…
I would prefer that America just bombs
North Korea before they can act.
Papa, I'm not talking about that.
I'm talking about the news
of those witnesses
accusing us of murder and corruption.
Oh, that news. That's what you meant.
Well, do you have an idea
who's behind that?
Do you think it's Camia Cruz?
[door closes]
[instrumental theme music playing]
I'm sorry. Did I wake you up?
Come here.
Why did you come home so late?
I was with our lawyer the whole day.
I want everything to go according to plan.
Have you eaten yet?
Yes.
You know, earlier, I saw everything on TV.
I thought about your father.
You probably don't know about it,
but he went up against
powerful people too.
He didn't back down from anything.
He wasn't scared of death threats,
and he wanted to right every wrong.
He would fight for it until the end.
You really took after him, Lily.
I guess I really did, Mom.
Since everything I'm doing now
is for our family.
Come here.
[Julio] I did a background check.
Camia Cruz is a former
public school teacher.
You wanted to kill her out of jealousy.
Now, you're telling me
I should worry about
a public school teacher?
You know, Emilia,
if Camia Cruz is still alive…
she's not a threat to me.
Although she is a threat to you.
Your unfaithful husband
will cheat on you yet again.
I'm telling you.
Keep an eye on him.
[Julio chuckles]
[Julio] ♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
[all] ♪ Happy birthday ♪
♪ Happy birthday ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
-[Julio] Cheers, everyone!
-[clapping]
A round of applause!
[Diego] We're almost there.
[Fernan groaning]
Diego, thank you.
If it wasn't for you,
I would've been dead by now.
Mister Fernan, violence isn't the answer.
What's gotten into you?
I get that, Diego.
But, you can't stop me now.
[Fernan] We have the same goal,
but different perspectives.
I just hope the day will come
when we'll work together
to fight against the Ardientes.
[groans]
Everyone, get some rest.
Some of you should come with me
so we can buy some things
we can give to the people.
Mike, get the bag.
[tense music playing]
[man] Congressman, a group of bandits
robbed the gambling den.
Seven of my men were injured.
We lost about 100,000 pesos.
Everyone knows you're
the gambling lord here.
Whoever did this has no respect for you.
They're not afraid of you.
Tell your men that I'm putting
up a 100,000-peso reward…
for every bandit they catch.
[Julio] They have nothing to worry about.
They will be rewarded with money…
whether they catch them dead or alive.
[line rings]
Yes, I'm looking for
Atty. Georgina Fisher.
I just want to ask something.
[woman over the phone] About what, sir?
Uh…
About the exposé that was aired earlier.
Is Camia Cruz your client?
Are you a reporter?
I'm afraid not, but I'm her boyfriend.
Uh, I just want to know where she is, and…
Hello? Hello?
Boyfriend?
Emilia. Camia is alive.
And when we see each other
again, I'm choosing her.
If that happens, she'll wish
she died in the fire.
And if you hurt Camia again,
I'll kill you myself.
[Fernan] Everyone, please fall in line!
Please don't push each other.
We'll make sure that each
and every one of you
will get food, bread,
and most importantly, money.
These goods are all for you.
We're just giving back what the
Ardientes have stolen from you.
[farmer 1] One at a time, everyone.
[Fernan] Please fall in line.
[Fernan] Come here.
Get your goods over here.
-[farmer 2] Here.
-[farmer 1] Ma'am, here you go.
[birds chirping]
[tense music playing]
Dress up, you two. We're going somewhere.
Where to, Papa?
We'll attend Governor
Alvarez's charity event.
We'll face the public and let them know
that we are one big happy
and loving family.
We'll also show them…
we aren't affected by those allegations
being thrown at us.
Because we are not guilty!
[Julio] Hey, Raul!
Don't you sneer at me like that!
I'm still talking to you two.
And also, don't forget
to wear something nice.
Why don't you take a bath?
[William] Look, they're here!
[reporter 1] Congressman!
[reporter 2] Congressman!
[reporter 3] Could you give a comment?
[Julio] Governor.
[William] Congressman, how are you?
[Julio] I'm fine, thanks.
[William] This way, please.
[reporter 1] Congressman!
What can you say about…
-[Ivy] It looks good on you.
-[Carlotta] Ivy!
We're live here in Poblacion Ardiente,
where the Ardientes will make
their first public appearance
since the exposé about the crimes
they allegedly committed was aired.
What can you say about
those accusations against you?
[Emilia] My dear friends…
I'm sorry, but we have no comment on that.
We're here for Governor
Alvarez's charity event.
We're here to help our constituents.
Is there any truth
to the allegations against you?
I'm afraid we can't comment.
Our lawyers will take care of this,
okay? I'm really sorry.
[reporter] Congressman, could you please
give a statement to your loyal supporters?
[Julio] I'm sorry.
I guess it's true that you
become more emotional
when you grow older.
Why are you getting emotional,
Congressman?
[reporter] Yes, Congressman?
It's very difficult for a father…
to see and hear someone
discredit his loved ones…
and tarnish his family's name.
I'm sure you know this already.
Ever since the beginning,
the core values I've taught my children
are excellence, honesty, and integrity.
[Julio] Despite all this,
I believe we can get through
this trying time.
Rest assured that we Ardientes
will continue
serving our constituents
in Poblacion Ardiente.
-[man] Liar! Murderer!
-[security 1] Who said that?
You shameless thieves!
[woman 2] We don't believe you anymore!
-Get out of here!
-Ouch!
[indistinct shouting]
Get out of here!
[security 2] Stop that! Stop that!
[woman] Get out of here, murderers!
Leave our town!
[townsfolk clamoring]
-[Jepoy] Stop it already!
-[woman] Liars!
[Emilia] Calm down, everyone!
[woman] Get out of here!
-Get them out of here!
-Get out of here!
Get them out of here!
They don't have a permit to hold a rally.
[man] You! You're a worthless governor!
You're just the Ardientes' lapdog!
[Emilia] That's enough. Calm down…
…friends. Listen!
[Emilia] Violence will
never solve anything.
-Let's stop this.
-[woman] You're a liar!
-[security 5] Hey!
-[security 6] Show some respect!
[security 7] Show some respect!
[indistinct shouting]
[Emilia] Friends! That's enough, everyone!
-[indistinct shouting]
-You!
Whoever's spreading rumors
about our family, come out!
Face us!
[tense music playing]
-Down with the Ardientes!
[crowd chanting] Down with the Ardientes!
Down with the Ardientes!
-[crowd continues chanting]
-[indistinct shouting]
[tense music playing]
[chuckles]
Did you see that?
The people are all furious now.
They're aware of how cruel
the Ardientes are.
I swear, Mom, this is only
the beginning of our battle
against the Ardientes.
I promise you, I'll make
sure they won't win this fight.
And every person they've wronged
will fight with us.
This is what I'll do.
I'll look for all
the victims Julio, Emilia,
and Raul have wronged.
I will talk to all of them
and urge them to file lawsuits
against the Ardientes.
Mom, this is it. What we've waited for.
We can finally have the justice
we want for Dad,
for what they did to you
and to our family.
The Ardientes are going down, Mom.
[Loring] They're lucky they
only got tomatoes.
Considering what they did,
they should be locked up.
I've experienced their cruelty, firsthand.
Let me ask you, Diego.
Who do you think is behind all this?
The right punishment for the Ardientes
isn't written in the law.
So I'll take it into my own
hands and deal with them myself.
Whoever it is, we should be thanking them.
The Ardientes won't stop
until they're dealt with.
They have the guts to go against
the Ardientes. It's inspiring.
Like what Fernan's group is doing.
[ominous music playing]
Mom, I've been thinking about
joining Mister Fernan's cause.
We'll get the cooperative
back from the Ardientes.
-We can fix this, Congressman.
-And how exactly do we do that?
What happened there?
What stupidity was that?
I thought you had a handle
on the charity event?
How did the press get in there?
And you even let those people
humiliate us in public!
You failed to protect us.
That alone is enough for me
not to trust you!
-But, Congressman--
-[Julio] Shut up!
Shut up and just leave, William.
And I better not hear any comment from you
regarding this issue. Now, get out.
Don't make me regret giving you
your position in office
and strip it from you.
Go and leave me!
If you were there with me, Arnaldo,
that wouldn't have happened.
I'm sorry.
I should've been there with you.
It's not your fault.
You had important business
at the city hall.
But what happened validates you
as my choice to take over
Poblacion Ardiente after me.
How can I trust someone like Alvarez?
All the while I thought
he was smart and quiet,
but he turned out
to be dumb and talkative.
To tell you the truth,
I'd actually choose your mother over him.
Of course. You trained Mom
-yourself, so--
-[Julio] Yes.
Until she threw it all away
when she bit the hand
that was giving her everything.
[Julio sighs]
[Emilia] In times like these,
one has to be
a sneak to get the best stuff.
[Claire chuckles softly]
Careful. Your Papa might find out
you're stealing from
his collection of vintage wines.
Aunt Claire, at the rate things are going,
I don't think he'll notice.
That's his karma
for banishing his only child.
Thank you.
Well Raul, let's toast to Papa's downfall.
[Claire] Madrigal, can I have
some, please?
-Cheers.
[Claire] You know what?
I like what you did earlier.
You challenged Camia Cruz to come out.
That was very bold.
[scoffs]
[Claire] Do you really think
she's behind all this?
If it really is her,
I don't think she'll come out.
The truth is, she's scared.
You know what bothers me,
Auntie? That Attorney Fisher.
There's definitely something
"fishy" about her.
But you know what? I did some research.
She's a big-time lawyer.
If it's true that Raul
locked up Camia for a long time,
I believe she's not
the only one behind this.
Someone big is backing her up.
Natalie?
She could've found out
you're the one who had her father killed.
[chuckles]
Auntie, I don't think she's bold enough.
I think it's someone
who has a grudge against our family.
Or someone who's very close to Camia Cruz.
[tense music playing]
Who could that be?
Could it be her darned daughter?
[Julio] Well, of course, my friend.
Well, clearly, this is
propaganda from our critics.
These are but false accusations.
Anyway, thank you for calling.
This issue will soon die down.
That Camia Cruz is becoming a problem.
Is she even real?
She is real.
And I can't deny that she's a threat.
But, obviously, she's not alone.
Someone's backing her up.
Then, who? Dad?
I don't think so.
No one in this household
would have the guts to do that.
They know I'm watching them like a hawk.
Do you know who I'm suspecting?
Miss Aguas.
[Emilia] You know, Auntie,
she could be alive.
Raul, what's the name of Diego's
best friend again?
I have to go out.
Madrigal, go with him.
[Emilia] You know, Auntie, at this point,
I don't really care
who's backing Camia Cruz.
My concern right now is how
to regain my old position.
The weaker Papa gets…
the bigger the chances of
taking him down are.
Good thinking.
[Julio] This all happened
while she wasn't in Ardiente.
[Julio sighs]
I don't get it. What does Ivy
have to do with Camia Cruz?
That is another thing
that we need to know.
And we also need to silence…
or twist the testimonies against us.
And more importantly, we need to know
where our enemies
are hiding those witnesses.
Okay, Grandpa. I'll handle it.
Do it as soon as possible.
We can't give them a chance
to file a case against us.
Ivy Aguas.
[Ivy] Very good, Attorney.
Our plan was a success.
Thank you, Miss Aguas.
I will file the criminal cases
against the Ardientes right away.
Okay. I'll send the media
to cover the case filing.
I want to bombard the Ardientes
with propaganda.
And before you leave,
I want you to do another thing.
Visit all the families listed there.
Convince each of them to testify
against the Ardientes.
The more families we have,
the more compelling our case will be.
This is very exciting, Miss Aguas.
Let's see if Julio's lawyers
can handle all the cases
we'll file against them.
[Fernan] Diego, thank you for helping us.
Mister Fernan, the cooperative
is important to all of us.
Most of us depend on it.
If we get it back,
we can start over again.
You're right.
Everyone, Mister Fernan,
can you please excuse us?
[Fernan] Okay. Everyone, let's go inside.
[tense music playing]
Dad, what are you doing here?
[Raul] I'm sorry for
interrupting your conversation.
I just want to ask you something.
Uh… Do you remember Lily Cruz,
your childhood friend?
Do you know anything about her?
Is she still alive?
[tense music swells]
I don't know.
I haven't heard anything
about her since she left.
Why do you ask?
I was thinking that Lily
might've found Camia first.
They might be together right now.
And they're both taking revenge
on Julio and Emilia.
I don't know, Dad.
[Raul] I'm sorry.
I just wanted to know how Camia was doing.
I hope she's fine, happy,
and safe. That's all.
Don't worry. We might not know
how Camia is,
but I'm sure they're about to get justice
for everything the Ardientes
put them through.
But I hope you know, Dad,
that they won't be
the only ones to pay for it.
You're guilty too. You were
their accomplice in everything.
Go back to the mansion, Dad.
You might get in trouble again.
Diego, son.
Forgive me.
I didn't want all this.
Take care of yourself.
[tense music playing]
Lily.
I was thinking that we could
have a stronger case if I--
Mom.
I don't agree.
But, Lily, this all started because of me.
Mom, I won't allow it.
I won't give them the chance
to ruin and tear us apart again.
Yes, I want us to face them together,
but I won't let any of us be hurt again.
Mom, I know what you feel.
I know you want to help.
Thank you, Mom.
But I want you to trust in my plans.
I assure you no one will get hurt.
And like I promised you,
those good-for-nothing Ardientes
will get what they deserve.
[tense music playing]
[goon 1] Let's have a drink, man.
[goon 2] Okay. I've been waiting
for you to say that.
[goon 2] Nice and cold!
Just the way I like it.
[goon 1] Why did our boss
make us guard this place?
Forget that. At least we have a job!
[goon 1] I'm going to pee.
[whispering] One. Two. Three.
Feels good.
-[goon 1] Hey!
-[grunts]
[Diego] That's enough! That's enough! Hey!
All right. Tie them up.
[Fernan] What should we do with them?
Just set them aside, Mister Fernan.
[Diego] We'll use them for later.
Okay, Mister Fernan.
Where's the key?
[goon 2] We don't have it.
-Where's the key?!
-[farmer] Give us the key!
-We don't have it.
-Do you want me to hit you?!
Just hand it over!
[Diego] Mister Danny,
where's the hammer? Move aside.
[goon 1] Hey! Don't do that!
[farmer 3] We're taking this back now!
-[farmer 1] Yes!
-[farmers cheering]
[Fernan] We did it!
[indistinct chatter]
Attorney, have you filed a case
against the Ardientes yet?
Yes, we filed multiple counts of murder
and a number of corruption cases
against Congressman Julio
Ardiente, Emilia Torillo,
Raul Torillo, and Arnaldo Torillo.
Do you have a message for the Ardientes?
I'm coming for all of you.
[Ivy] I won't stop as long as
there's an Ardiente in power
with the freedom to do what they want.
I'll make sure all of them
will rot in prison.
Attorney Georgina.
You're a woman of your word.
You work really fast.
I'm not only fast. I'm also good.
I know, I know. Too bad you'll be…
using your skills for something
you'll regret later on.
[chuckles] Are you threatening
me, Mr. Ardiente?
You know, it's been a while
since someone called me "Mister".
Because you don't deserve
to be called "Congressman".
Ouch!
You are a dirty politician,
and I will bring you down.
Oh, my! Now, let's not get
ahead of ourselves, attorney.
A lot of things can still happen.
Your client, for example.
Camia Cruz, is she?
For all you know, she just might
suddenly drop dead even before
the case hearing starts.
Camia Cruz is not my client.
Oh! Who, then? Ivy Aguas?
I don't know that woman.
Is she one of your angry mistresses?
I like you, Attorney. You're funny.
Such a shame you're playing
for the losing side.
Anyway, once I have this case dismissed…
I'll get rid of you next.
I will destroy your career.
I will make you regret the day
you decided to take up law.
Bring it on, Mr. Ardiente.
I'm not afraid of you.
[blows raspberries]
Such a feisty woman!
I'll love a challenge like her.
-[Loring laughing]
-[indistinct chatter]
[Loring] Isn't this great?
[crowd laughing]
You know, those people
who helped us are real heroes.
True.
And because of these seeds,
we can finally plant again.
[cheering and clapping]
Do they work for the Ardientes?
[Fernan] Yes. They do.
[Danny] They were guarding the warehouse.
[farmer 5] You're the guy who pushed me!
[Loring] People like them
deserve a good beating.
[all cheering]
[indistinct pleading]
[farmer 6] Or better yet, why
don't we let the ants bite them?
-[all] Perfect!
-Please don't.
[crowd cheering]
[laughing]
[farmer 6] I didn't know
they're comedians.
So, everyone, what are we waiting for?
Let's arrange these goods
so we can start selling them.
-Okay.
-Okay. Game.
Okay. Back to work.
[exhales]
What are you doing here, Congressman?
Oh.
You're the judge handling handle
the case against me, right?
So, do you want it thrown out?
Yes.
Then, you must give the court
compelling evidence
that you didn't steal
from the public funds…
and you didn't have anyone killed.
I see.
[tense music playing]
Is one million pesos compelling enough?
Oh! And with it, comes a
promotion to the highest court.
I'm sure you'd like that, Judge Rivera,
to be called Justice Rivera
of the Supreme Court.
It's got a nice ring to it.
Are you really this scared
that you need to bribe me?
No. It's not that I'm afraid.
I just want this petty case
dismissed as soon as possible.
[Judge Alice breathes heavily]
Then I'm sorry, Congressman.
Because you can't buy me.
The case will proceed, as usual.
And once we find out you're guilty…
I won't think twice before
unseating you from your position
and locking you up!
I see.
Well…
[grunts]
You know, it seems like…
everybody has been threatening me lately.
So now it's my turn to give my warning.
Julio Ardiente's wrath
is like a hurricane.
It will destroy everything in its path.
I'm ready for you, Congressman.
[Ivy chuckles]
Well, Attorney,
I'm not surprised he said that.
But don't worry.
Like the witnesses in this case,
I will protect you.
Thank you, Miss Aguas.
Oh, by the way…
Julio's under the impression
you're the one behind all this.
[chuckles]
I know. In fact, I already have
a solution to that problem.
But, Lily, aren't you worried
he might have the case dismissed?
And what if he turns his attention to you?
Mom, I'm not afraid because we
have solid evidence against him.
And the judge handling the case
is on the side of justice.
She can't be bought with money.
What about you, Lily?
What if Julio finds out that
you're the one behind all this?
Once that happens, I'll face him.
And on the day he gets arrested
to be sent to prison,
I'll be there.
I want to see his reaction
when he's put behind bars!
[tense music playing]
[crickets chirping]
[tense music swells]
[Atty. Georgina] You don't deserve
to be called "Congressman".
You are a dirty politician,
and I will bring you down.
You can't buy me. The case will proceed.
And once we find out you're guilty…
I won't think twice before unseating you
from your position and locking you up!
I can't understand…
why some intelligent people…
become fools because of their principles.
[suspenseful music playing]
[grunts softly]
[phone dialing]
Hello?
I'm counting on you, my friend.
-Don't worry.
-Okay.
Um… I'll see you in the office.
-Sure.
-Okay.
[suspenseful music playing]
[motorcycle engine humming]
[suspenseful music swells]
[Judge Alice] Fred, let's go. Hurry.
[clinking]
Why did you stop?
I told you to drive faster!
Fred, come on!
-No!
-[muffled gunshot]
[suspenseful music swells]
[motorcycle engine humming]
JUDGE COMMITS SUICIDE
[screams]
[Ivy] Suicide?!
Who does that
congressman think he's fooling?!
I'm sure! I'm very sure he had her killed!
[exhales sharply]
Don't worry about it, Mom. We'll
use this against the Ardientes.
Attorney! We'll tell everyone
what really happened.
Because the judge didn't commit suicide
but was killed by the Ardientes!
Say that in the press conference!
That's what I want you to do. Now!
They can fool everyone, but not me! Never.
Thank you for the promotion, Señor Julio.
I've always wanted to be an RTC judge.
It's nothing, Vince.
After all, your father
and I are very close.
Well, now that you're the judge,
you know what to do.
I'll take care of the cases
filed against you.
Good. Very good.
[clinks]
JUDGE RIVERA WAS A KNOWN
HUMAN RIGHTS ADVOCATE
HANDLING THE NUMEROUS CASES
AGAINST THE ARDIENTES.
I'm sure Ivy's case will be
compromised because of this.
I need to help her.
[Atty. Georgina] This is clearly
an attack on human rights.
We do not believe that
Judge Rivera killed herself.
She was killed so that the real
criminals could escape justice.
[reporter] Are you saying that
Congressman Ardiente
ordered Judge Rivera to be killed?
We won't stop until the deaths
of these innocent people
are given justice.
[Atty. Georgina] Those who are
drunk with power will pay.
We read that Camia Cruz is one
of the proponents of the case.
Where is she?
Why doesn't she show herself?
-Yes, where is she?
-Yes, Attorney.
Where's Camia Cruz?
We want to hear her story.
Is someone protecting her?
We need a statement on this, Attorney.
[reporter 3] What is she afraid of?
[reporter 4] Yes, Attorney.
Where is Camia Cruz?
[reporter 2]
We read that Camia Cruz is one
of the proponents of the case.
Where is she?
Why doesn't she show herself?
[reporter 5] Yes, where is she?
[reporter 3] Yes, Attorney.
Where's Camia Cruz?
We want to hear her story.
Miss Aguas, you have a visitor.
Ivy.
Diego, what are you doing here?
Someone might've followed you.
No, Ivy. I'm sure of that.
I found out what Grandpa did to the judge.
I want to help you.
Diego, we've already talked about this.
Ivy, listen to me. This isn't
just about your parents.
It's about my mother too.
Can't you see we both
have the same goal here?
I wanna do something to prevent
this case from being dismissed.
Ivy, you can trust me. I'll help you.
Even if I have to testify
against the family
who raised me, I'll do it.
[Atty. Georgina] He's right, Ivy.
We need all the help that we can get now.
I spoke to the judge earlier,
and he's inclined to dismiss
the case if Camia won't show up in court.
Hey!
Come, join me.
Sit down. Sit down.
Join me.
Drink.
Eat.
Ha!
Isn't it wonderful to see
my wicked family complete?
[Julio chuckles]
Um, are we celebrating something?
Yes, we are celebrating my victory.
Has the case been dismissed, Julio?
Uh…
Well, not yet. But, I'm getting there.
This case will be dismissed
without Camia Cruz
in the picture.
And I tell you, it's impossible
for her to show up because she's a coward.
-Ivy, I have to come out.
-Mom, no.
Ivy, I didn't get this second
chance just to remain in hiding.
It's about time for me to face them--
No, Mom. It's too dangerous.
I won't let you do this.
Ivy, we can't always live in fear.
Because if we do, the Ardientes
will continue holding us
by the scruff of our necks.
If other people can
testify in court for this,
I'll do my part too.
Let me do it because this is my fight.
This is our fight.
And if we continue to be afraid,
we can't solve this, Ivy.
Well then, Papa, congratulations!
But, don't you think
the public should know
about our celebration?
What do you mean?
[Emilia] Well Papa, you see,
our enemy's tactic is to
humiliate you through the media.
Then why not also celebrate
our victory through the media?
Let's have a grand press conference.
[Claire] Actually, it's the
perfect timing, Julio.
Especially now that our enemies are weak.
Mom, if that's what you want.
If you're going to face them,
then I will too.
Let's do it together.
Ivy, no. I'm the only one
who'll come out in the open.
Because you have to continue our fight
if something happens to me.
I won't let you do that, Mom.
Just like what I promised you,
I'll protect you from the Ardientes!
We will fight, Mom. The two of us.
[tense music playing]
[Julio] You know, this
family could have been
much more powerful
if we only worked together.
If you didn't go against me before…
our enemies wouldn't have seen
the chink in our armor.
But, I won't let that happen again.
Anyway, Emilia,
you set the press conference.
We'll face the public as one family.
Strong and united.
Perfect!
-[Emilia chuckles]
-To the Ardientes.
[Diego] Leave it to me.
I'll make sure they'll testify
against the Ardientes.
Just be careful, Diego.
And thank you. I appreciate your help.
You know I'd do anything for you.
[romantic guitar music playing]
See you, Ivy.
I'll be going, Mrs. Camia.
Lily, I know that our battle
has only just begun.
We'll have more challenges to face.
But one day, you'll be happy.
And Diego too.
[phone rings]
Emilia.
[Emilia] Hi, Ivy.
How are you?
I hope you're well-rested now.
I need your help.
[chuckles] Why do you need my help?
Well…
We're having a grand press conference
for Papa tomorrow
to fix the mess that, you know…
So I want you to come with me.
It's fine with me.
But what about the congressman?
I thought he was mad at me.
Well, my dear, this is the perfect time
for you to fix your mess
with the congressman.
Don't worry, I'll back you up.
Good idea. All right, Emilia.
I'll be there.
See you.
Brilliant! Bye, dear, take care.
Mom. I know where you're going
to make your big reveal.
I like that smile, Emilia.
Smile of success, Aunt Claire. Tomorrow,
the crowd will be cheering
the name of Emilia Ardiente.
[chuckles]
You know, Auntie, it might even
give Papa a heart attack.
That press conference
will bury him into the ground.
He's in for a big surprise.
That's more like it.
[Emilia] Papa, look who's here!
[Julio] You know,
I was under the impression
you were hiding from me
because you did something wrong.
[Ivy] Is it because I'm one
of your suspects
behind the attacks against you?
[host] Let's welcome the Ardiente Family!
[Emilia] You know, Camia Cruz,
if you're telling the truth,
then come out. Show yourself.
[Camia] Well, Emilia? Cat got your tongue?
Or would you prefer this?
Why the long face?
[theme music playing]